hellotv.in 2014-12-28

# Hello TV: FREE Live TV Channels Online | Videos | Movies | Mobile TV | Latest TV News Online

##### HelloTV is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users

This privacy policy tells you how HelloTV, a division of PK Online Ventures Pvt Ltd uses personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. We strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

##### Collection of Information

HelloTV uses one or more third party ad serving technology to serve ads at this site and at our clients' sites. In the course of delivering an ad to you, the third party ad serving party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfil your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner.

##### Cookies

"Cookies" are strings of text that a web site transmits to a user's computer. Cookies enable a website to keep track of a user's preferences and activities relating to that website. Our website creates a temporary cookie for each visit in order to facilitate the visit. These cookies automatically expire as soon as you leave our website.
